mygeodata.cloud 2018-11-03

# MyGeodata Cloud - Privacy Policy

GeoCzech, Inc. (as a MyGeodata Cloud owner) processes your personal data in the following way:

#### SCOPE OF PROCESSED PERSONAL DATA

We process the following personal data of our customers to whom we provide our services and who communicate with us via e-mail:

  * Email address
  * First and/or Last Name
  * Billing address
  * IP address

When you register for MyGeodata we ask for information such as your name, email address, billing address, credit card information. Members who sign up for the free account are not required to enter a credit card. We aggregate information on what pages consumers visit, and information volunteered by the consumer (such as survey information and/or site registrations). The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Web pages and the quality of our service, and is not shared with or sold to other organizations for commercial purposes, except to provide products or services our customers have requested, when we have their permission, or under the following circumstances:

#### PURPOSE OF PERSONAL DATA PROCESSING

MyGeodata uses collected information for the following general purposes:

  * products and services provision
  * billing
  * identification and authentication
  * services improvement
  * contact
  * research

We do not store credit card details nor do we share customer details with any 3rd parties.

#### WHO AND HOW TO PROCESS PERSONAL INFORMATION

MyGeodata will process your personal data to the above-defined extent and for the above defined purposes, mainly in electronic form using automated systems and will be processed by our own employees.

#### VOLUNTARINESS OF CONSENT TO THE PERSONAL DATA PROCESSING, THE POSSIBILITY OF CONSENT WITHDRAWAL

Granting consent to the processing of personal data is entirely voluntary. The consent can be withdrawn at any time by sending the withdrawal of consent to the email address supportmygeodata.cloud.

#### YOUR RIGHTS AS A DATA SUBJECT

  1. You are entitled to request from MyGeodata Cloud access to your personal data and information about your personal data and its processing (e.g. scope, purpose, time of processing), including the right to provide a copy of the processed personal data.
  2. You are entitled to withdraw consent at any time (for details see point 4).
  3. You are authorized to request in writing to erase your personal data (in particular when you withdraw your consent to the processing of your personal data or in the case where personal data are no longer needed for the purpose for which they were collected or processed).
  4. You are entitled to obtain our personal data processed by us in a commonly used, structured and machine-readable format.
  5. If you believe that we process your personal data in violation of your privacy, or in violation of law or regulation, especially if personal data are inaccurate with regard to the purpose of processing, you may, upon written request:

  * object to the processing of your personal data
  * ask us for an explanation
  * require us to resolve the resulting situation, in particular, it may be blocking, repairing, adding or deleting personal information

#### COOKIES

A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, that is sent to your browser from a web site's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive.  
Cookies are required to use the MyGeodata service.  
We use cookies to record current session information, but do not use permanent cookies. You are required to log-in to your MyGeodata after a certain period of time has elapsed to protect you against others accidentally accessing your account contents.

#### STATEMENT ON EU GDPR

In accordance with [European Parliament Regulation 2016/679](http://eur-lex.europa.eu/legal-content/EN/TXT/HTML/?uri=CELEX:32016R0679&from=en) (General Data Protection Regulation), this Regulation does not apply to our services (see paragraph No. 23).

#### DATA STORAGE

MyGeodata uses third party vendors and hosting partners to provide the necessary hardware, software, networking, storage, and related technology required to run MyGeodata. Although GeoCzech, Inc. (as a MyGeodata owner) owns the code, databases, and all rights to the MyGeodata application, you retain all rights to your data.

#### CHANGES

We may periodically update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your MyGeodata primary account holder account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.

#### QUESTIONS

Any questions about this Privacy Policy should be addressed to supportmygeodata.cloud.
